A Guide to the League of Women Voters of Virginia records, 1920-2011
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Publications., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 69-77)
  - Subseries 6: Reference books and Directories, 1 box (Box 76)
    - Reference books and directories, 1987-1988. (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Reference books and directories, 1988-1990. (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Reference books and directories, 1990-1994. (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Directories, 1999-2001. (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Directory and reference book, 2006-2007. (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Directory and reference book, 2008-2009. (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 7: Miscellaneous Files, 1 box (Box 77)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1965-1979. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1980-1981. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1982-1984. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1985-1989, 198[-]. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1990-1996, 199[-]. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous papers, no date. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Tax, 1977-1992. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Sales and use tax certificate of exemption, 1977-1979. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Sales and use tax certificate of exemption, 1980-1981, 1983-1984. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Sales and use tax certificate of exemption, 1991-1993, no date. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - List of tv stations and newspapers. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Lists. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Video--League of Women Voters Running and Winning the high school program When You Say Leader. (Box 77)
    - Video--It's Incredible--League of Women Voters of Waynesboro, VA--Seventy-Fifth Jubilee Celebration, 18 February 1995. (Box 77)
    - Video--Decision Richmond. (Box 77)